Are you awake, Arata?
（炯(けい)）起きたか 灼(あらた)
What happened to me?
（灼）俺 どうしたの？
You collapsed on the street.
You don't remember?
（炯）路上で倒れたそうだ
覚えてないのか？
Oh, yeah. It was right after I met
with Governor Komiya...
そっか 小宮(こみや)都知事と
会ったあと急に…
Did you perform a Mental Trace?
メンタルトレースをしたのか？
I told you not to do it
when I'm not there.
俺がいない時は
やるなと言っただろう
So, what about Karina Komiya?
で 小宮カリナは？
She wasn't involved
in Dr. Tsuchiya's death.
土谷(つちや)博士の死には関与してない
そっちは？
And you?
I met with a former Unit One inspector.
前任の一係監視官と会ってきた
Tokorozawa Correction Center
Ex-Inspector Kira,
I believe you know this man?
（炯）来良(きら)元監視官
この男をご存じですね？
According to your case records,
捜査記録によれば
あなたと相棒の伏瀬(ふせ)監視官は―
you and your partner, Inspector Fuse,
were investigating a smuggling case.
密貿易事件の捜査中だった
Your suspect, however,
died in an unforeseen accident.
だが その被疑者が突然
事故で死亡した
Right.
（来良）そうだ 被疑者が
最後に会っていたのが―
That man was the last person
the suspect met with.
その男だった
You investigated Koichi Azusawa?
（炯）この梓澤廣一(あずさわこういち)を捜査対象に？
We couldn't connect him to the accident.
（来良）
事故との関連は見つからなかった
After that, the two of you
were in a car accident as well.
その後 あなたたちも
車両事故に遭った
You were severely injured
and Inspector Fuse died.
あなたは重傷を負い
伏瀬監視官は死亡
Records show maintenance errors...
記録では多数の整備ミスが原因
A fox did it.
（来良）狐が やったんだ
A fox?
狐？
It's a lead Fuse found.
伏瀬が つかんだ情報だ
A criminal syndicate whose members
can maintain their Hues.
色相を保ったまま犯罪を犯す組織
They call themselves "foxes."
狐と呼ばれているらしい
You think this man is one of them?
（炯）この男が その１人だと？
We couldn't find anything.
（来良）
俺たちは何もつかめなかった
Please, don't ask any further.
これ以上は勘弁してくれ
There are foxes
in the Public Safety Bureau, too.
狐は公安局にもいる
"Foxes." The Suppressing Action
Department officers used that word too.
狐… 行動課の人も
そう呼んでたね
But we still don't know
だけど梓澤廣一という男が
パズルのどのピースかは不明
where Koichi Azusawa
fits into this puzzle.
I checked his history. He's changed jobs
dozens of times in a short period.
（炯）経歴を調べたが
短期間で何十社も渡り歩き―
Current affiliations are unknown.
It's like he vanished into thin air.
今は所属不明
空気のように消えた
But he leaves tracks.
でも足跡は残る
In the memory of a former inspector,
for instance.
例えば前任監視官の
記憶の中とかにね
I'll trace him and...
俺がトレースして…
Ow!
ぐっ いった～！
Your intracranial pressure is elevated.
（炯）脳圧亢進(こうしん)の兆候ありだ
（灼）うう…
No Mental Traces for now.
（炯）しばらく
メンタルトレースはやめろ
There's no need to make a fuss.
（灼）大げさだなあ もう
I'm just fine, Kei.
俺は大丈夫だよ 炯
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
♪～
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the lost memories that flee
once they're liberated and banished
Are an everlasting cubism.
Cause I know that in a future gone mad,
Even nightmares are peaceful.
RESET, RESET, yeah.
The midnight sun
awakens and turns to a riot.
A gun for a faux-friendly kiss.
A knife for a faux-revolutionary hug.
Get rid of it all, even the frozen chains.
Reality is always outside your head.
In a world seen through bestial eyes,
There is neither darkness nor light.
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the false memories that flash before
your eyes impatiently and impulsively
Are an everlasting cubism.
～♪
#05
Agamemnon's Offering
（おなかの鳴る音）
（小畑(おばた)のため息）
I'm back.
（梓澤）ただいま～
はい 小畑ちゃん 出島(でじま)のお土産
Here, Obata dear. A souvenir from Dejima.
I don't want it.
（小畑）いらねえよ
（梓澤）ハァ… あっ
Special Religious Zone Briefing
So this Inspector's making his move next?
次は あいつが動くんだってねえ
And here I thought he hated games.
ゲーム嫌いのインスペクターなのに
Let's see what he can do.
お手並み拝見
（小畑）くっ… ガア～ッ！
Why'd you give him the card?
（入江(いりえ)）何で名刺を渡したんだよ
Remember how everyone suspected us
of the former inspectors' accident?
（入江）前任の事故の件で―
俺らが さんざん疑われたの
忘れたのかよ
I'm lending them a hand so they don't get
any weird ideas about us!
（天馬(てんま)）変な勘ぐりされねえために
こっちから手を貸すんだよ
You just don't get it.
分っかんねえやつだなあ
I don't think either of them would
suspect us just because we're enforcers.
（雛河(ひなかわ)）あの２人なら
執行官というだけで―
疑うことはないと思うけど
I wonder.
（如月(きさらぎ)）どうだか
尻尾を振るのは勝手だけど―
You're free to wag your tail for them
all you like, but keep me out of it.
私を巻き込まないでよね
（ドアが開く音）
Don't forget me
（如月）くっ…
No Special Religious Zone!
（日本人）宗教特区 反対！
（デモ団体）宗教特区 反対！
Impeach Governor Komiya!
Get out, immigrants!
（日本人）入国者は出ていけー！
Immigrants will cloud our Hues!
（デモ団体）入国者は出ていけー！
No Special Religious Zone!
（日本人）宗教特区 反対！
（デモ団体）宗教特区 反対！
Get out, immigrants!
（日本人）入国者は出ていけー！
（デモ団体）入国者は出ていけー！
Mitake New Town
Special Religious Zone Briefing
（日本人）宗教特区 反対！
No Special Religious Zone!
（デモ団体）宗教特区 反対！
All drones in position.
（雛河）
ドローンの配置 完了しました
Thanks. Great work.
はーい ご苦労さまです
I heard you were investigating
what happened to your predecessors.
あの 前監視官の事故
調べてると聞きましたが
We've got nothing to show for it yet.
（灼）まだ成果なしです
I see.
（雛河）そうですか
Just on security detail for the governor.
I'll bring Arata.
（炯）今日は都知事の
警備任務だけだ 灼も連れてく
Yes, we've got to perk him up.
ああ 少しは精をつけさせないとな
A "city for immigrants"?
Times sure have changed.
（天馬）入国者の街たあ
時代も変わったもんだ
Isn't the governor's Affirmation Party
anti-immigrant?
（如月）都知事の肯定党(こうていとう)は
反移民派よね？
Mitake New Town is a model for renewal
and a valuable constituency.
（炯）三郷(みたけ)ニュータウンは
地方復興モデルで大事な票田
It'll also act as relief
for the mortgage collapse.
この前の住宅ローン破たんの
救済にも活用されている
It can't be ignored.
無視できないのだろう
The time has finally come for this town
to be reborn as a special religious zone.
（カリナ）ついに
この街が信仰特区に―
生まれ変わる日が
来ました
All restrictions imposed
on proselytism
これまで入国者の皆さんに
制限されていた―
and religious activities
will be lifted here.
布教や宗教行事も
ここでは全面解禁されます
I'm so happy for all of you.
みんな ハッピーです
（拍手）
♪～
"Happy."
（カリナの歌声）
（アウマ）ハッピー…
It's actually
an ingenious segregation policy.
（カリナの歌声）
（トーリ）
実態は巧妙な隔離政策ですよ
At least it's better
than ending up in the slums.
（陵駕(しのぎ)）
スラム行きよりはマシでしょう
I wouldn't mind. The slums offer order
for those with no place to belong.
（アウマ）拙僧は かまわん
この国のスラムには
居場所なき者のための秩序がある
Do you plan to accept this
without protest?
（トーリ）抵抗せず
受け入れるおつもりですか？
No. I will ignite myself if necessary.
（アウマ）否 必要なら
我が身に火を放とう
Forget self-immolation. Fire-fighting
drones are good at their jobs.
焼身自殺なんて およしなさい
今どきの消火ドローンは優秀よ
Besides, it's not what Sibyl would want.
それにシビュラ的ではない
We must prove that faith purifies the Hue.
信仰が色相を清めると
証明すべきでしょう
Just a holo recording?
Why isn't the governor here in person?
（久利須(くりす)）録画ホロだけで―
都知事本人が来ないとは
どういうことだ
Risk assessment.
（オワニー）リスク判断です
The protest was larger
than our predictions.
反対デモが予想以上の規模でしたし
ご理解ください
Please understand.
（通話が切れる音）
チッ
I see you're still holding onto
that thing.
（陵駕）まだ それを
持っていてくれたのね
What do you want?
何の用だ
How's your condition?
（陵駕）体は どう？
Stage four. I don't have much longer.
（久利須）ステージ４だ
もう長くはない
Is that why you sped up acceptance
of the special zone?
（陵駕）それが特区受け入れを
早めた理由？
You must understand.
君も分かっているはずだ
We may have ended isolation,
but this country hasn't changed.
開国を成し遂げても
この国は何も変わらなかった
Change takes time.
変化には時間が必要よ
I don't have time.
私には それがないんだ
You still have time
to watch over the child.
あの子を見守る時間は まだある
ハァ…
（雛河）
ん？　あれ 故障… かな？
Huh? Is it malfunctioning?
Did something happen?
どうかしましたか？
It's showing an odd area stress response.
妙なエリアストレス反応が
Deploy everything to its location.
出現地点をすべて出してください
♪「FIRE BURNING WOMAN」
～♪
Inspector!
監視官
Kei, watch the stage.
炯 ステージを警戒
Roger.
了解だ 行くぞ
Let's move.
Good grief.
（天馬）ハァ… やれやれ
（歌声）
（拍手）
（マルセルの荒い息）
Crime Coefficient is 153.
Target for enforcement.
（ドミネーター）
犯罪係数153 執行対象です
Non-Lethal Paralyzer.
ノンリーサル･パラライザー
（マルセル）ぐっ…
あっ ああ…
Audi nos!
アウディノース！
Everyone, get down!
あっ 全員 伏せろ！
Kei!
炯！
（警報）
Don't you think the boy's at his limit?
（裁園寺(さいおんじ)）あの坊や
もう限界だと思わない？
Yes, the time may be ripe.
（代銀(しろがね)）ふむ 確かに頃合いだね
I'll take that as a "yes."
（裁園寺）
いい返事と受け取るわよ
If I recall correctly, there was
a friendless congressman once before.
（代銀）確か以前も
孤立したコングレスマンがいたな
Toya Saionji, I believe his name was.
裁園寺陶治(とうや)君だったか
I won't end up like my brother.
（裁園寺）兄のようにはならないわ
As Sibyl evolves,
シビュラの進化に従い―
fewer and fewer people can cross
the dangerous bridge of Bifrost.
ビフロストという
危うき橋を渡れる者は―
ますます限られていく
Look away,
and you'll end up head over heels.
よそ見をすれば真っ逆さまだ
Sorry I'm late.
（静火(しずか)）お待たせしました
Invest in rural infrastructure.
（静火）
地方インフラにインベスト
Promote scanner installation.
スキャナー配備を推進
厚生省の管理能力を強化
Enhance Ministry of Welfare regulation.
Favoring Public Safety as always,
but gentle judgment, considering.
相変わらず公安局びいき…
の割には おとなしいジャッジね
So, even our bold Shizuka
is at the end of his rope.
勇敢な静火君も
いよいよ後がないか
Dealer's judgment.
親のジャッジよ
Invest in major news agencies. Guide
public opinion to favor the special zone.
大手報道各社にインベスト
特区推進へ世論を誘導
（ゲームの開始音）
Judgment confirmed.
（ラウンドロビン）ジャッジ確認
Congressmen must participate in all
judgments until the relation concludes.
リレーション完結まで
コングレスマンは―
すべてのジャッジに
参加しなければなりません
Leaving your seat except at set times
and other obstructive behavior
規定時間以外の途中退席
および妨害行為は―
will result in enforcement action.
執行対象となります
We're investigating
the suicide bomber's identity and motive.
（炯）自爆犯の素性 動機
共に調査中
We think it involves
the Special Religious Zone.
状況から信仰特区がらみと
思われます
Collect evidence
to prevent further crimes.
（霜月(しもつき)）裏を取って
さらなる犯行の防止を
Find out everything about
where the bomb came from.
爆弾が どこから来たか
徹底的に解明しなさい
Yes, ma'am.
（２人）了解
Also, I assume you remember Sasagawa?
それと 些々河(ささがわ)のこと
覚えてるわね？
The suspect in the subprime case?
サブプライム事件の容疑者
Didn't Foreign Affairs' SAD arrest him?
外務省行動課が拘束したのでは？
He's dead.
死んだわ 出島で移送中
車両事故に遭ったそうよ
Apparently the car transporting him
to Dejima was in an accident.
Was it really an accident?
本当に事故ですか？
Foreign Affairs is investigating.
（霜月）外務省が調査中
They provided data
from his pre-transport questioning.
移送前の尋問について
情報提供があった
Sasagawa mentioned Koichi Azusawa by name.
些々河の口から
梓澤廣一の名前が出たわ
The man our predecessors
were pursuing, right?
（炯）前任の監視官が
追っていた人物ですね
I authorize you to view
classified materials up to level two.
課長権限で機密レベル２(ツー)までの
閲覧を許可する
Consider links to the terrorist bombing,
爆弾テロとの関連も考慮し―
and study up on the foxes.
狐について学んでおきなさい
The suicide bomber was an immigrant
named Marcel Cotard.
（志恩(しおん)）自爆犯は―
入国者
マルセル･コタール
We've learned he was a factory worker in
New Town who went missing six months ago.
ニュータウン内の工場労働者で―
半年前から
行方不明だったことが判明
How did he get a bomb
through the hazardous material sensors?
そいつは どう爆弾を抱えて
危険物センサーをスルーしたんだよ
It was embedded in his body.
（志恩）体に埋め込んだの
In his stomach? That's crazy.
（天馬）腹ん中？
とち狂ってんな
Remember how the area stress
was going up and down?
（志恩）エリアストレスが
出たり消えたりしたでしょ
It seems he was drugged
into a hypnotic state.
薬を使って
催眠状態にされてたみたい
Meaning we can speculate that
someone else masterminded the attack.
つまり首謀者は他にいると
推測される
Aiming to massacre
special zone supporters?
（如月）動機は
特区賛成派の抹殺ですか？
Seems that way.
（志恩）そうね
会場にいた賛成派は１名を除き死亡
All but one supporter in the venue died.
Its opponents, in contrast, all survived.
逆に反対派は全員生存
Theresa Shinogi.
テレーザ陵駕
Former refugee advocate in Dejima and
leader of the anti-special-zone faction.
元出島の難民弁護官で
特区反対派の筆頭
Next, Joseph Auma.
（炯）次が
ジョセフ･アウマ上人
Leader of the New Town factory workers.
ニュータウン
工場労働者の顔役だ
Torri Aschenbach.
（灼）トーリ･
アッシェンバッハ
Agent for the founder of the authorized
religious group Heaven's Leap.
公認宗教団体―
〝ヘブンズリープ 〞の
教祖代行です
Not the founder?
代行？
The founder was the first
Sibyl-authorized religious leader
教祖はシビュラ認定初の
公認宗教家で―
and hasn't appeared
in public in six months.
半年前から表に出ていないそうです
Smells fishy.
Could they be more suspicious?
くさいな いかにもって感じだぜ
By the way, the suicide bomber Marcel
was a follower of Heaven's Leap.
ちなみに自爆したマルセルは―
ヘブンズリープの信者だという
情報あり
That settles it. Let's go enforce them.
決まりだろ
とっとと執行しちまおうぜ
There is one more suspect.
（志恩）あと１人 怪しいのがいる
（天馬）あん？
Kurisu Kyoji O'Brien.
（志恩）久利須
矜治(きょうじ)･オブライエン
An observer for the Immigration Bureau.
入国管理局オブザーバー
His Hue has deteriorated
over the past several months.
過去 数か月
色相を悪化させ―
It exceeded permissible values
following the bombing.
爆発直後に既定値を超過
If the theory holds, he was involved.
（如月）
セオリーどおりなら―
事件に関与した
But he checked himself into
a psychological care facility last night.
（志恩）ただし 昨晩すぐに―
自分からメンタルケア施設に
入所してる
And he's the organizer of the PR event.
それに彼
ＰＲイベントの主催者なの
He should have no motive
to cause terrorism.
（炯）本来なら
テロを起こす動機がないか
They all seem suspicious.
なんか 全員うさんくさいですね
Heaven's Leap has the Bureau of Culture's
backing. They're trouble.
特にヘブンズリープは
厚生省文化局の肝いりだし
かなり やっかいだな
You know about them, Shindo?
慎導(しんどう)君 詳しいの？
Just a little, through my dad's work.
父の仕事の関係で少しだけ
I thought Sibyl was a product of science.
シビュラはさあ 科学の成果だろ？
Why would it authorize religion?
何で宗教なんか認めるんだよ
But you believe in crystals
and Feng Shui and stuff, right?
天(てん)さんだって信じてるだろ？
水晶とか方角が どうとか
That's statistics.
あれは統計学だ
There's no God anyway,
so we may as well get rid of religion.
どうせ神様なんて いねえんだから
宗教なんて全部ぶっ潰せよ
I wouldn't be so sure.
（灼）それは どうでしょう
（天馬）ん？
It's not a question of
whether or not there is a God.
神様って いるかいないかが
問題じゃないんですよ
Just being conscious of Heaven
and Hell changes how people act.
地獄や天国を意識しただけで
人の行動は変わりますから
Religion does have a violent history,
and Sibyl is wary of that.
宗教に不幸な歴史はあるし
シビュラも それを警戒してる
However, faith isn't that simple.
でも信仰は
そんなに単純なものじゃない
Do you believe in something, Inspector?
監視官は何か信じてんのかい？
No, but most prejudice
stems from ignorance.
（灼）いえ ただ偏見の多くは
無知が原因です
Ignorance?
（天馬）無知？
（灼）あっ 今のなしで
Oh, forget I said that.
You can't take it back once you say it.
（天馬）吐いた唾
飲み込むんじゃねえよ
That's enough.
そこまでにしておけ
Start by checking everyone involved
for links to bombs.
まずは関係者を当たり
爆弾につながるか調べる
A bomb hunt? Give me a break.
爆弾探し？　勘弁してくれよ
Come on, let's get going on
another fun day on the job!
（手をたたく音）
（灼）さあさあ
今日も元気に出動しますよ～
フー…
Shion.
志恩さん お願いがあるんですけど
I need a favor.
What, again?
何？　改まって
We're up against dangerous people. I want
to bring in that legendary lady detective.
やっかいな相手ばかりですから―
今回も伝説の女デカの力を
お借りしたくて
On this case?
Can you guarantee her safety?
この件で？
安全を約束できるの？
I will.
します！
Kurisu O'Brien is in care. He can wait.
ケア中の久利須･オブライエンは
後回しだ
Arata, make sure you don't
perform any Mental Traces.
灼 くれぐれも
メンタルトレースは使うなよ
Yeah, yeah, I know.
は～いはい 分かってるってば
I'm Torri Aschenbach. I represent
the founder of Heaven's Leap.
ヘブンズリープ 教祖代行の
トーリ･アッシェンバッハです
Forgive my presumption, but I welcome you
as a fellow protector of Psycho-Passes.
せん越ながら―
同じく人々のサイコパスを
守る者として歓迎いたします
Thank you for your cooperation.
ご協力 感謝します
Now, go ahead.
（トーリ）さあ どうぞ
（炯）ん？
Point your Dominator at me.
It's your duty, is it not?
ドミネーターを私に
それが務めのはず
Crime Coefficient is 19.
Not a target for enforcement action.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数19
執行対象ではありません
What a clear Hue.
（信者）なんてクリアな色相
I'd expect no less.
（信者）さすがは代行様
Would the latent criminals
please wait here?
では潜在犯の方々は
こちらで お待ちください
We request that you not enter the church.
教会内の立ち入りは
ご遠慮願います
What was that?
ご遠慮だ？
I want to avoid trouble.
Remain on standby.
トラブルは避けたい
待機しててくれ
ハァ… あいよ
Fine.
Warning. Link not fully established.
（コミッサ）
警告 リンクの確立が不完全です
Check your connection environment.
通信環境を確認してください
You're blocking signals?
電波遮断を？
Throughout the whole church.
屋内は すべてね
It's so that we may preserve our Hues
and face Sibyl with pure hearts.
色相を守り 清らかな心で
シビュラと向き合うためです
Almost like a quarantine facility.
まるで隔離施設ですね
We aim to be prepared for anything.
万全の態勢を心がけていますから
You know him?
お知り合いで？
This was once a medical facility.
It has ties to the athletics world.
（トーリ）元は医療組織ですので
アスリート界と縁が深い
If Mr. Yakushiji
had won the gubernatorial election,
先の都知事選で薬師寺(やくしじ)さんが
当選していれば―
this tragedy would never have occurred.
今回の悲劇も起きることはなかった
What a pity.
残念ですよ
Are you aware that the suicide bomber
was one of your followers?
自爆犯が ここの信者だったことは
ご存じですね？
Are you certain?
何かの間違いでは？
Positive.
（炯）確かです
Why did you leave the stage
before the blast?
爆発前にステージを離れた理由は
どうしてですか？
As an act of protest.
（トーリ）抗議のためですよ
I'd hate to be a suspect
simply because I escaped harm.
難を逃れただけで疑われるのは
心外ですね
Why oppose the special zone?
（炯）なぜ特区に反対を？
Limiting where people can live
based on religion is unconscionable.
（トーリ）信仰を理由に居住地を
制限するなど もってのほか
Especially as it is not an oracle from
Sibyl, but the governor playing politics.
それもシビュラの神託ではなく
都知事の政治的な都合など論外です
Is that what your founder teaches?
それも教祖の教えですか？
Yes. It is a sacred teaching
to guide all people.
ええ 万人を導く尊い教えです
I would like to meet Founder Nisei.
（炯）仁世(にせい)教祖と
会わせていただきたい
Unfortunately, he entered a special state
of prayer six months ago.
残念ですが半年前から
特別祈とうに入られ―
No one knows when it will end.
いつ終わるか誰にも分かりません
I can exercise my authority to compel him.
強制権限を行使することもできます
That won't work.
それは無理でしょう
Why not?
なぜですか？
Do you know how many believers
we have in the Ministry of Welfare?
厚生省に教団の信者が
どれほどいると お思いで？
In fact, we may soon wield Dominators
on equal footing with Public Safety.
むしろ我々が公安局と肩を並べ―
ドミネーターを手にする日も
近いでしょう
I doubt Sibyl would authorize it.
（炯）
シビュラが認めるとは思えない
You'll understand soon.
すぐに分かる
We merely await the oracle.
我らは ただ神託が下るのを
待つのみです
I'm sorry for the sudden request,
Ms. Kunizuka.
（灼）急なお願いで すみません
六合塚(くにづか)さん
Don't worry about it.
I'll help in any way I can.
（六合塚）気にしないで
私にできることなら協力するわ
I won't let it be like the Giga Arena.
ギガアリーナみたいなことは
させません
I don't mind. I'm used to it.
別に かまわないわよ
慣れてるし
That's our legendary lady detective!
さすが伝説の女デカ
Stop calling me that.
それは やめて
Abandon selfish desire.
Let us attain Nirvana together.
（僧侶）
我欲を捨て 共に泥(ない)おんの境地へ
Thank you for complying, Venerable Auma.
応じていただき感謝します
アウマ上人
I care not.
It was a favor for you, after all.
かまわぬ
他ならぬ お主の頼みだ
I'm Inspector Arata Shindo.
監視官の慎導 灼です
Did you plan the incident the other day?
先日の事件
あなた方の計画ですか？
Hey!
ちょっと
Point your ray gun at me
if you want to know.
知りたくば
お主らの光線銃を向けよ
I think I'll take you up on that offer.
へえ それじゃ遠慮なく
Crime Coefficient is 26.
Not a target for enforcement action.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数26
執行対象ではありません
That's too clear for an old ex-guerrilla.
元ゲリラのジジイが
クリアすぎだろ
Watch your mouth.
口に気をつけなさい
Oh, I'm so scared.
おお～ 怖っ
I attained enlightenment
atop a mountain of corpses.
拙僧は しかばねの山にて
悟りを得た
（２人）あっ
Is this real?
（灼）本物ですか？
Don't be afraid.
The explosives have been removed.
恐れるな 爆弾は抜いてある
Joseph Auma survived
an explosive misfire and found Buddhism.
上人はゲリラ時代に
爆弾の不発で生き残り―
仏法に目覚めたの
What else would you ask?
他に何を問う？
Do you believe the suicide bomber
acted alone?
自爆した人物は
単独犯だと思いますか？
No. He was merely controlled.
否 操られたにすぎぬ
Who do you think controlled him?
どんな人物が操ったと思いますか？
Probably an amateur. Had it been me,
there would be no survivors.
素人であろうな
拙僧であれば １人も生かさぬ
Any ideas about the explosives they used?
使用された爆薬に心当たりは？
We have laid down all our weapons.
我らの武器は すべて手放した
It was the price for my brethren
to dwell in this land.
同胞が この国に根づく代償として
This is your turf, isn't it? You say
you don't know where the bomb came from?
この辺りは あんたのシマだろ
なのに爆弾の出どころを
知らねえってのか？
Cut it out.
（六合塚）あなたね…
Practice asceticism.
精進するのだ
When you extinguish your flame of rage,
you too may be as she is.
怒りの火を滅却した時
お主も彼女のようになれる
Follow the right path,
and you will meet the one you wait for.
正しき道を行けば
待ち人に会えるであろう
A lecture from an ex-guerrilla boss?
Seriously?
（入江）
ゲリラの元親玉が説教とはね
Now, now.
（雛河）まあまあ
What's the "right path"?
“正しき道”って何です？
The CRP, Council of the Right Path.
正道(せいどう)協会 ＣＲＰのことね
A refugee protection group in Dejima.
They manage the infrastructure here.
出島の難民保護団体で
ここのインフラも運営してるわ
Look.
ほら
Sister Theresa Shinogi represents them.
代表者はシスター･テレーザ陵駕
団体立ち上げに尽力した宗教家よ
She's a religious leader and founder.
Our next target.
次の調査対象ですね
接触できますか？
Can you contact her?
Yes, of course.
（六合塚）ええ もちろん
What?
えっ？　はい すぐに向かいます
Yes, we'll be right there.
What's going on?
どうしました？
Trouble over the terrorist attack.
先日のテロがらみでトラブルよ
シスターが仲裁に向かってる
The Sister is going to mediate.
May the Lord's blessings
and grace be with you.
（陵駕）あなたたちに
主の祝福と恵みを
Everyone should be able to find happiness,
no matter their circumstances.
人は皆 どんな状況でも―
幸せを見つけることが
できるはずです
We know.
（工員）分かったよ
Oh my, Ms. Kunizuka.
あら ミス六合塚
I'm sorry you had to see that.
見苦しいところを
見せてしまったわね
I'm impressed you were able
to mediate alone.
お一人で仲裁されるなんて
さすがです
All she did was pay them off.
金で追っ払っただけだろ
That's enough out of you.
いいかげんにしなさい
Money is their god.
お金が彼らの神なのよ
I'm glad things worked out.
無事に解決して何よりです
Would you give me a moment,
Inspector Arata Shindo?
ちょっとだけ待っていて
慎導 灼監視官
We'll speak afterward.
話は そのあとで
あ…
He looks like the bomber.
自爆犯にそっくり
This is Ishak,
the bomber Marcel's twin brother.
（陵駕）イシャクよ
自爆したマルセルの双子の弟です
We shouldn't let him go, then.
なら逃がしちゃまずいだろ
He doesn't know anything.
Marcel vanished six months ago.
彼は何も知らないわ
兄は半年前に失踪して それっきり
Please let us interview him.
一応 聴取をさせてください
Would you tell us about your brother?
お兄さんのこと
話してくれませんか？
Marcel's Hue was getting bad,
so he joined Heaven's Leap.
（イシャク）兄貴は―
色相がやばくて
ヘブンズリープに入ったんだ
Said it beat being institutionalized.
施設行きよりマシだって
Did he contact you after vanishing?
彼が失踪してから接触は？
No.
ないよ
I was honestly relieved he was gone.
正直 いなくなってホッとした
ストレス解消に俺を殴るから
He used to hit me to blow off steam.
I believe you can tell
he's telling the truth?
（陵駕）あなたなら
ウソではないと分かるでしょ？
Yes, it appears he is.
ええ そのようです
Now, before we begin,
please point your guns at me.
（陵駕）さっ まずは
あなたたちの銃を向けてちょうだい
You heard the lady.
（灼）だそうです
Fine.
（入江）はいはい
Crime Coefficient is 22.
Not a target for enforcement action.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数22
執行対象ではありません
Clear.
クリア
That's quite clear,
considering that bombing.
あんな事件のあとなのに
きれいですね
That is the fruit of my faith.
日々の信仰のたまものよ
You think blowing people up is faith, too?
爆弾で吹っ飛ぶのも信仰だってか
On the contrary, that's the path
of nihilism that has lost faith.
それは逆ね あれは信仰を失った
ニヒリズムの道
Faith ought to be a safety valve
to stop extremist ideas from taking root.
信仰は本来 過激思想を
根づかせないための いわば安全弁
In that way,
the special zone makes sense.
その意味で信仰特区は
間違いではない
So why do you oppose it?
（灼）では なぜ反対を？
A good ideology is meaningless
if it's poor in practice.
理念は正しくても運営がダメなら
意味はないわ
Oh, and speaking of practice,
how is Kurisu O'Brien's condition?
そうそう 運営といえば―
久利須･オブライエンの様子は
どう？
He's undergoing emergency care.
施設で緊急ケア中です
Then I suppose I can rest easy for now.
（陵駕）なら ひとまず安心かしら
Mr. O'Brien is pro-special-zone, right?
オブライエン氏は推進派ですよね？
We're estranged now,
but we're old comrades from Dejima.
今は疎遠だけど
出島時代からの仲なの
He was a founding member of the CRP.
ＣＲＰの創設メンバーでもあるのよ
You protected refugees there?
出島で難民保護を？
Yes. That's why we protested
against isolationism.
ええ そのための
開国運動をしてたわ
I also knew Nisei,
the founder of Heaven's Leap, at the time,
ヘブンズリープの仁世教祖とも
その頃に知り合ったけど―
but we lost contact when
his current representative took over.
今の教祖代行になってからは
連絡が取れなくて
You're very well connected.
顔が お広いんですね
Not as well connected as your father.
（陵駕）あなたの父上には
かなわないわよ
You knew my dad?
父を知っているんですか？
He helped us to establish the CRP.
（陵駕）ＣＲＰの立ち上げを
助けていただいたの
You were young at the time,
and he was always worried about you.
当時 父上は ずっと
幼いあなたを気にかけていたわ
I see.
そうですか
Parents always worry about what path
their children will choose.
（陵駕）親は子が―
将来 どんな道を選ぶのか
気が気でならない
Take care that seeing things that aren't
there doesn't lead you down a dark path.
あなたも存在しないものを
見るあまり―
暗闇の道を選ばないようにね
I will.
はい
Now, I must prepare for mass.
（陵駕）
そろそろミサの準備をしないと
Would you care to join us?
あなたたちも参加してみない？
We'd love to, but we have work to do.
残念ですが仕事がありますので
Time may have stopped for this boy,
（陵駕）この子の時間は
止まってしまったとしても―
but that doesn't mean
you should follow suit.
あなたまで
そうなるべきじゃないわ
What did your father do in Dejima,
Inspector Shindo?
（入江）慎導監視官の親父さん
出島で何してたんすか？
Something about exporting Sibyl.
シビュラの輸出やなんかを
Because of that,
I lived in Dejima for a while myself.
それで俺も 一時期
出島で暮らしてたんです
Wasn't that in my file?
俺のファイルに
ありませんでした？
No, we didn't look that...
（入江）いや そこまでは… あっ
Honestly, dear.
（舞子(まいこ)）ホント この人ったら―
You should have told me you were hurt,
even if it wasn't serious.
大したケガじゃないからって
言わないんだから 勝手すぎる
Wow, he didn't tell you?
（灼）あらら 言ってなかったの？
Maybe Kei's keeping other secrets
from you.
炯ったら
他にも秘密があったりして…
Of course I'm not.
あるわけないだろ
Well, it really was minor,
and he got it protecting his comrades,
実際 軽傷だし
仲間を守った名誉の負傷だから―
so he didn't want to show it off.
Right, Kei?
自慢するみたいで
恥ずかしかったんだよね 炯
Yeah.
（炯）ん…
More importantly, I hear your operation
is coming up. Congratulations!
それよりさ いよいよ手術だね
おめでとう
Thank you, Arata.
（舞子）ありがとう あっちゃん
But is it really all right? There are
many people worse off than I am.
でも いいのかな
もっと苦しんでる人もいるのに
Don't think that way.
There's no reason you should suffer.
それは違う
お前が苦しむべき理由なんてない
I'm sure your mom feels the same.
お母さんも そう思ってるはずだ
That's right.
（灼）そうだよ
天国で舞(まい)ちゃんに―
She's up in heaven,
wishing for you to be happier.
もーっと幸せになってほしいって
思ってるよ
Thank you.
ありがとう
So, is what's happening now
related to our case?
ねえ 今 起こってること
私たちの事件と関係あるのかな
It's too soon to say.
まだ何とも言えない
Whether it is or not, we'll solve it.
そうであっても なくても
俺たちが解決するよ
Don't forget our promise.
約束 忘れないで
Whatever truth we uncover,
we'll trust each other.
どんな真実であっても
お互いを信じ続けるって
Yeah.
（灼）ああ
Mai almost never asks
about cases like that.
（灼）珍しいね 舞ちゃんから
事件のこと聞くなんて
It's the bombing. She's worried there'll
be conflict like in our motherland.
爆弾のせいだ
母国のように紛争が
起こるんじゃないかと心配してる
And it's not as though this country
has completely accepted us.
それに俺たちは完全に
受け入れられたわけじゃない
This country is progressing,
little by little. So is our case.
この国も少しずつ進んでる
俺たちの事件の解明も
ハァ… レベル２止まりとはいえ
機密の閲覧を許可されたしな
We can view classified data now,
although only up to level two.
There wasn't much on Koichi Azusawa, but
something about the foxes caught my eye.
梓澤廣一に関して
大した情報はなかったが―
狐について気になる点があった
You mean that someone is scouting them?
誰かがスカウトしてるって
とこでしょ
Exactly.
そうだ 些々河も榎宮(えのみや)も―
Sasagawa and Enomiya were both scouted
and under the control of an organization.
より上位の組織に見いだされ
命令を受けていた
The foxes are growing in number,
and they're organized.
（灼）狐は増える
個人でなく組織として
My dad had the same card.
父さんも同じ名刺を持ってた
Don't leap to conclusions.
Atsushi was a good person.
早合点するな
篤志(あつし)さんは立派な人だ
Akira was a good brother, too.
輝(あきら)さんだって
立派なお兄さんだったよ
There must be a reason.
We'll uncover the truth over time.
理由があるはずだ
少しずつでも答えに たどりつくさ
Listen, maybe if I Mental Trace
the suicide bomber, we'll...
あのさ 自爆した男の
メンタルトレースをすれば―
何か… うっ わあっ！
（急ブレーキの音）
No Mental Traces. Period.
メンタルトレースはやるな 絶対だ
I know, I know.
分かったって
I hope so.
（炯）ならいいがな ほら
（灼）えっ？
Go on.
We're here. Rest and take it easy today.
（炯）着いた
今日は ゆっくり休んで寝ろ
Fine.
（灼）あ… はい
You were young at the time,
and he was always worried about you.
（陵駕）父上は ずっと
幼いあなたを気にかけていたわ
Dad.
父さん…
What?! This case is none of your business!
（霜月）はあ？
あんたらの出る幕じゃないでしょ！
It involves anti-isolation policy.
（花城(はなしろ)）事は開国政策に関わる
When you make your move, so will we.
そちらの動きしだいでは
こちらも動くと言っておくわ
Then give us your intel!
だったら情報をよこしなさい
I'm supplying you with as much as I can.
（花城）可能なかぎり
提供しているでしょう？
Remember to keep our activities in mind.
くれぐれも我々の行動に
留意してほしいわね
I'll do what I can.
可能なかぎりはね フンッ
Good morning, Venerable Auma.
（灼）
おはようございます アウマ上人
Did you take the right path, Shindo?
（アウマ）
慎導 正しき道を進めたか？
ん… ボチボチです
I took a few steps.
You say you've found evidence?
重要な証拠が見つかったと
Yes. One of the church's medical drones
was stolen a short time ago.
うむ 少し前に教会の
医療ドローンが盗まれたと―
Sister Shinogi consulted me about it.
シスター陵駕から相談された
One of my followers found the drone,
それを我が信徒が
見つけたのだが―
but it seems it may be related
to the bombing.
どうも先日の一件に
関係がありそうなのだ
Thank you for reporting it.
通報に感謝します
No need to thank me.
（アウマ）礼には及ばぬ
Please stop those sad fools
who seek to meet their end in fire.
火をもって終末を迎えんとする
愚かで悲しき者を止めてやってくれ
The timing of his report is too perfect.
（炯）このタイミングで
情報提供は都合がよすぎるな
Yeah, but it doesn't seem malicious.
（灼）だよね 悪意は感じないけど
What about Sister Shinogi?
教会のシスター陵駕は？
She hasn't come to the church
since she left yesterday.
（灼）昨日 外出したまま
教会に戻ってないって
I'll ask our analyst.
分析官に捜してもらう
Tell me when you get results on the drone.
ドローンの解析結果が出たら
教えてくれ
We'll join you once we interview O'Brien.
オブライエンの聴取が
終わりしだい合流する
Public Safety.
公安局だ 1703号室に入所中の―
I'm here to see Kurisu Kyoji O'Brien
in room 1703.
久利須＝矜治･オブライエンに
会いにきた
Let me check. Please wait a moment.
（受付ホロアバター）
確認します お待ちください
He's actually here?
マジで ここにいんのか？
They say pharmaceutical companies
run experiments here.
製薬企業が実験してるって
悪名高いとこだぜ
Experiments?
実験？
They're only rumors.
あくまでウワサですが
My apologies. Mr. O'Brien
is currently seeing a visitor.
（受付ホロアバター）
申し訳ございません
ただいま来客中です
しばらく お待ちください
Please wait.
What do we do?
どうしますか？
Use our authority to enter.
強制権限で立ち入る
That's the spirit!
そう来なくっちゃな
No legal sales data.
Must be a black market drone.
（入江）正規の販売記録なし
闇流れのドローンだな
They don't have enough doctors.
医師不足を補うためよ
違法だけど大半が黙認されてるわ
It's illegal, but mostly tolerated.
Where'd it originally come from?
（灼）もともとの出どころは
分かります？
Probably Dejima.
出島でしょうね
実は嫌なウワサがあるの
There are some nasty rumors
that Sister Shinogi seizes property
in exchange for immigration assistance.
シスター陵駕は出島の
入国あっせんの見返りに―
財産を没収してるって
Now you mention it, Auma mentioned
having to give up weapons.
そういえばアウマ上人も
言ってましたね
武器を手放したと
I've finished restoring
the recording data, Inspector.
（雛河）監視官
記録データの復元完了です
It's the real deal.
（入江）マジもんだぜ
It implanted bombs in human bodies
using an organ transplant program.
臓器移植プログラムの応用で
体内に爆弾を埋め込んでます
The surgery was performed five times.
手術回数は ５件
Meaning there are four more out there.
つまり 残り４発ある
（爆発音）
（炯たち）うっ！
Kisaragi, evacuate the patients!
（炯）如月は収容者の避難！
Todoroki, with me! We'll secure O'Brien!
廿六木(とどろき)は俺と来い
オブライエンを保護する
This is O'Brien's room.
オブライエンの部屋か 彼を捜せ！
Find him!
（天馬）んっ あ…
Looks like we found him.
見つけたみてえだぜ
だいぶ形が変わっちまってるがな
Not in the way we wanted him, though.
Collating data.
This is Kurisu Kyoji O'Brien.
データ照合
久利須＝矜治･オブライエンです
くっ…
This second bombing
was in the city center.
（霜月）今度は都心で第２の爆破
You were there and couldn't stop it?
現場にいて何で止められないの？
My apologies.
面目ありません
The bomber was another member
of Heaven's Leap.
自爆犯は今回も
ヘブンズリープ信者
The sect denies entrance
for Hue preservation.
教団は色相保護を理由に
立ち入りを拒否
I'll negotiate with them.
What about the bombs?
そっちは私が交渉する 爆弾は？
Evidence suggests there are three more.
We're searching for them now.
証拠から残り３発あると推測され
行方を捜索中
Any suspects?
容疑者は？
The anti-special-zone faction.
特区反対派の犯行と見て調査中
But the Hues of all its representatives
were clear.
ただし代表者たちの色相は
全員クリアでした
No leads at all?
手がかりゼロ？
もう！　被害者に何か特徴は？
Anything special about the victim?
The victim, Kurisu Kyoji O'Brien,
had terminal cancer.
殺された久利須･オブライエンは
末期ガンだったと判明
They murdered a man at death's door?
余命わずかの人間を
わざわざ殺した？
Unless they didn't know.
あるいは知らなかった
Oh, and regarding Sister Shinogi,
え～ ちなみに
シスター陵駕ですが―
records show she visited
O'Brien's hospital room last night.
記録によれば 昨夜
オブライエンの病室を訪れてます
We don't know where she is now.
その後 行方が分かりません
And the medical drone used for the bomb
transplants was purchased in her name?
（霜月）爆弾移植に使用した
医療ドローンの購入者も―
彼女の名義なのね
Yes, but I don't think she is...
（灼）
はい ただし彼女の犯行とは…
It's enough for a household search!
Now go solve this case!
家宅捜査には十分
即刻解決 行きなさい！
Usage of illegal drugs on immigrants
was uncovered at the bombed facility.
（炯）爆破現場の施設で
入国者への違法な薬物使用が発覚
It's all over the news.
ニュース沙汰になってる
Hence the strict information control?
それで報道規制が厳しいのか
Politicians supporting Heaven's Leap
have also lodged complaints.
ヘブンズリープを支持する
政治家からも―
かなりの抗議が来ているそうだ
No wonder the chief was pissed off.
（灼）そりゃ 課長もキレるわけだ
They beat us twice.
２度も やられた
We'll stop them the third time.
３度目は必ず止める
Kaboom!
（入江）ドカ～ン！
（天馬）うおっ
Give it a rest, idiot!
（天馬）やめろ バカ！
（入江）へヘヘヘッ
The caregiver drone's
life-support program is running.
介護ドローンの延命プログラムが
実行中です
Who was it treating?
誰を治療してたんでしょう？
Life-support?
（炯）延命…
（灼）ん？
No luck. Nothing's coming up.
ダメです 特に何も出ません
（ドアの開く音）
Same here, damn it.
（入江）こっちもだ クソッタレ
We turned the place upside down
and came up empty?
（天馬）こんだけ
ひっくり返して空振りかよ
I wouldn't say so.
（灼）そうでもなさそうですよ
（一同）ん？
A report on a terrorist attack in Dejima.
（志恩）過去に出島で起きた
テロの報告書
Lists of smuggling groups.
Data on crimes concerning immigrants.
密売組織のリスト
入国者がらみの犯罪データ
She really could be behind it.
テロの主犯でも おかしくないわね
The nun's gotta be our perp.
犯人は尼さんで間違いねえだろ
執行して 一件落着だ
Let's enforce her and get it over with.
Except she's gone into hiding.
当人は行方を
くらませちまったがな
There were also documents on the New Town
warehouse district's management.
（志恩）あとは―
ニュータウン倉庫街の
管理書類もあったわ
Many of the warehouses are jointly owned
by Mr. O'Brien and Sister Shinogi.
多数の倉庫がオブライエン氏と
シスターの共同所有になってる
Seems the car rental's
administrative server
確か リースカーの
管理サーバーにも―
showed Auma moving something
from the factory to those warehouses.
同じ倉庫へ アウマ上人が―
工場から何かを
運んだ記録がありました
So, they were all
in a smuggling racket together?
（入江）こいつら全員が組んで
ブツを流してたってか？
If so, the anti-special-zone faction
feared its creation would expose them,
もし そうなら―
特区成立で密輸が告発されることを
恐れた反対派が―
and murdered its supporters.
We have a motive.
推進派を殺した
という筋書きになるか
（灼）う～ん
But what about Heaven's Leap?
I doubt they're uninvolved.
でも例の教団は？
無関係とは思えませんが
Well, I found something strange
about their founder's representative.
それね 教祖代行を調べたけど
変なのよ
He started a company at 13
and became its CEO.
13歳で起業 ＣＥＯに就任
He went on to own 18 different businesses
before becoming a religious leader.
以降 18社の企業のオーナーを
歴任し宗教家に
What's up with that?
（入江）何だ こりゃ
Is that kind of career change
even possible?
（如月）
こんな転職 可能なんですか？
Well, it's not illegal, at least.
（志恩）まあ 違法ではないわね
Sounds just like Koichi Azusawa.
似てるね 梓澤廣一に
（２人）あっ…
フー… で 教団だけど―
So, about Heaven's Leap.
They regularly make large deliveries
out of the country,
オブライエン氏が担当していた
国賓を通して―
through state guests received
by Mr. O'Brien.
定期的に大量の何かを
国外へ送ってるわね
フー…
あ…
Smuggling via state guests?
国賓を使った密貿易
That damn cult is a smuggling ring?!
あのクソ教団！　密輸業者かよ
If the freight in the warehouses
is involved,
倉庫街の荷物と関係するなら
シスターを教団が かくまったか
Heaven's Leap
could be sheltering the sister.
We need to find out
what they're shipping overseas.
彼らが何を海外へ運んでいるのか
突き止める必要がありますね
Then we have two targets:
The warehouses and Heaven's Leap.
（入江）
じゃあ 倉庫と教団 的は２つだな
I'll help.
私も手伝うわ
Wait a minute.
There are three bombs left, remember?
（志恩）ちょっと
爆弾が３発も残ってるのよ
So? I can't back out now.
だから？　今さら手を引けないわ
I'll keep her out of danger.
危険なことは させませんよ
That said, we don't have the chief's
approval to investigate Heaven's Leap yet.
とはいえ 教団のほうは
課長許可が下りてないんですが
About that.
それだが―
Heaven's Leap had a photo on display
of this man on the state guest.
国賓リストにある この男
教団で写真が飾られていた
The acting leader's relative...
教祖代行の血縁 叔父ですって
An uncle, apparently.
（ノック）
（ザハリアス）ん？
Mr. Viktor Zaharias, I presume?
ヴィクトル･ザハリアスさんですね
Cooperate with us
or face compulsory questioning.
強制聴取か 我々に協力するか選べ
What? What do you want me to do?
（ザハリアス）な… 何だ
何をさせる気だ
（霜月）ふっ！
（コミッサ）わ～っ！
You arrested a state guest
for a covert investigation?!
国賓滞在者を軟禁して潜入捜査？
Yes, ma'am.
You did say "any means necessary."
はい 課長が手段を問わないと
"Go solve this case!"
即刻 解決しろと
（コミッサのうめき声）
（霜月）くっ… ふっ！
Enforcer Hinakawa
is producing an infiltration holo.
雛河執行官が
現在 潜入用ホロを作成中
We'll begin as soon
as we have your approval, ma'am.
課長の許可をいただければ
すぐにでも開始します
What goods are he going to receive?
そいつが受け取る荷物は何なの？
We'll find out once we infiltrate.
それも潜入すれば分かります
If you screw up,
you'll hit the ground so hard...
しくじったら
お前ら 地獄に落とす！
（コミッサ）ああ～っ！
Yes, ma'am!
（灼･炯）了解
Compatibility and Aptitude Examination
Sibyl's compatibility examination
results came back.
（志恩）シビュラの
相性適性診断の結果―
Our undercover investigators
will be Kei and Mao.
潜入捜査員は
炯君と真緒(まお)ちゃんに決定
But I was planning to do it.
（灼）
俺が やるつもりだったのに～
ん？
You're a "D" with everyone.
What are you, a social misfit?
（炯）全員とＤ判定だぞ
社会不適合者か お前
Is that how you talk
to a fellow inspector?
同じ監視官に向かって
その言い方は どうだろう
It's a pleasure, Kisaragi.
よろしく頼む 如月
Yes, sir.
は… はい
（入江）ぬうう…
What?
なっ… ぐっ！
Are you screwing with me?
（入江）ふざけてんのか？　えっ！
（雛河）あっ… 何ですか？
What do you mean?
National Center for Medical Research
I'm sorry,
I won't be able to accompany you.
すまない 付き添いが
できなくなってしまって
I'm fine.
You're the one who should be careful, Kei.
私は平気 炯こそ気をつけて
Don't worry.
心配ない
Your operation will go great, Mai.
手術は必ず成功するよ 舞ちゃん
Thanks, Arata.
ありがとう あっちゃん
Operating
I can't believe I'm praying to God.
I thought I'd lost faith a long time ago.
神に祈るなんて
とっくに信仰を
なくしたつもりだったのに
Maybe you got to see her off
before infiltrating because you prayed?
潜入前に見送りができたのは
神様に祈ったおかげじゃない？
Maybe.
そうかもな
The holos can only operate continuously
for up to four hours.
（雛河）ホロの連続稼働は
４時間が限界です
Remember to keep them charged.
こまめに充電してください
Communication is impossible
inside the facility.
（志恩）
施設内は通信支援は不可能
Find a way to get outside
when you want to contact us.
連絡したい時は
何とかして外に出てね
Yes, understood.
ああ 了解だ
Kisaragi.
（入江）如月
What?
（如月）何？
If things get hairy,
I'll come to the rescue. Don't worry.
やばくなったら すぐ助けにいく
安心してくれ
（口笛）
ヘッ
Do you not trust me?
（如月）信用してないの？
It's time. Let's go.
（炯）時間だ では行こう
Yes, sir.
（如月）はい
Don't worry about Mai.
舞ちゃんのことは心配しないで
炯が戻るまで俺が見守ってる
I'll keep an eye on her while you're gone.
We'll find the sister
and prevent the next terrorist attack.
シスターを見つけ
次のテロは必ず阻止する
♪～
Stupid perfection in your own castle
How smart. You cause me to yawn
Look,
The key to the door is in your hand
Don't you let anyone take control
What do you want?
Go get it. Play by your own rule
The winner always controls the game
You stand in your belief
There's no promising future
Always helpless
Crying for the moon
Finger trembles in fear
With the weight of the trigger
There's a way for us
Show them how we fight
Pull the trigger
～♪
"Psycho-Pass" refers to the measurement
of a person's mind and personality.
This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance
to real persons or groups is coincidental.